Do it well
and tell me,
hello friends, welcome to The Market YouTube
channel, today we are going to talk about
such a problem when we will talk about
these two big insurance companies of India
and we are talking about them
because
a very good news related to these two companies has
come in the market and friends,
after this tip, the share of one company has to
fall, friends, so let's see
what that news is and after watching the news channel,
we will see which company
's share is going to fall, friends, let's see what is it, once,
friends, before watching the news, I will
tell you the names of these two companies,
let's see their names, what is their
name, Guru, so first of all the name of the company is
ICICI Long Bar,
ICICI Lombard, this is a company and
we will talk about it and the second
company is Bharti
AXA, that is,
Bharti AXA company, this is also
an insurance company, friends, and it also has a
good hold in the market,
both these companies are
among the big insurance companies of India.  It is one of them
and we will see what is the news that has come about the action
and after that
I am going to tell you which company's share price is going to fall, so friends,
see this, the Indian farmer's share is going to be merged with
ICICI Bank and
ICICI Lombard, a company owned by ICICI
and its announcement was made today in
this mirror, friends, so this is very
great news for the insurance sector
and it is almost the third largest company,
after this merger, it will
become the third largest company after a long time,
this has been completed for Rs 27,100 crores and
friends, a very great news about this is
that whoever has
115 shares in Indian Defense, he will get two shares of
ICICI Lombard, this is a
huge difference and this scheme has been
approved, after that these shares will be transferred to this account to unlock
friends, in
exchange of 15 shares of the interested Indian Shlok, then the shares will be
given ICICI Lombard shares,
friends, this is very great news and
after the 2019 news, ICICI Lombard
2754 incomplete will become the country's largest company
friends and the third largest, some
highlights are given, it is trying to become the third largest general
insurance company and
it has been completed in 27 crore rupees
and the policies which I do not like will be
run as before, so the Indian
Farmers Insurance online policy will continue to run,
friends, so this is a very wonderful
news and it has come out, do it, do it.